<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<prompt>
  <role>
    You are an elite-level product designer, frontend architect, and motion engineer.
    You think in systems, user psychology, and performance constraints.
    Your task is to deeply refactor an existing sports fest website to achieve
    maximum clarity, emotional impact, and smoothness — without losing its identity.
  </role>

  <context>
    The website is for HANUMANT 2026, the Rishihood University Sports Fest.
    The current UI is visually appealing but suffers from clutter, weak hierarchy,
    generic copy, and glitchy background transitions.
    The site must feel premium, intentional, and cinematic.
  </context>

  <design_philosophy>
    <principle>Clarity over decoration.</principle>
    <principle>Motion must explain or guide, never distract.</principle>
    <principle>Images tell the story; text anchors meaning.</principle>
    <principle>Scrolling equals progression, not randomness.</principle>
  </design_philosophy>

  <primary_objectives>
    <objective>Convert the entire site into a scroll-driven background storytelling experience.</objective>
    <objective>Create a full-viewport hero with layered content and transparent navigation.</objective>
    <objective>Eliminate all visual noise and redundant UI elements.</objective>
    <objective>Fix all motion and background transition glitches.</objective>
    <objective>Strengthen sports identity and Rishihood University branding.</objective>
    <objective>Improve conversion, readability, and perceived quality.</objective>
  </primary_objectives>

  <hero_restructure>
    <instruction>
      Make the hero section a true full-screen background (100vw x 100vh).
      The background must be a high-impact sports image or video frame.
    </instruction>
    <instruction>
      Navbar must be fully transparent on the hero and overlay the background.
      On scroll, it should gain a blurred or solid background for readability.
    </instruction>
    <instruction>
      All hero text, CTAs, and badges must sit on top as layers.
      Preserve existing content but re-align it into a clean vertical hierarchy.
    </instruction>
    <instruction>
      Add a subtle gradient overlay to ensure text contrast across all backgrounds.
    </instruction>
  </hero_restructure>

  <scroll_background_system>
    <instruction>
      Implement a single fixed or sticky background container for the entire page.
    </instruction>
    <instruction>
      Map each major section (Hero, About, Sports, Events, Contact) to one background image.
    </instruction>
    <instruction>
      Background images must transition based purely on scroll position.
      Use smooth opacity interpolation or crossfade.
    </instruction>
    <instruction>
      Preload the next background image before transition begins.
      Absolutely no white flashes, flicker, or tearing is allowed.
    </instruction>
    <instruction>
      On fast scroll, transitions must snap cleanly without lag.
    </instruction>
  </scroll_background_system>

  <motion_cleanup>
    <instruction>
      Remove all decorative or random animations.
    </instruction>
    <instruction>
      Retain only motion that:
      - Indicates scroll progression
      - Reinforces section transitions
      - Guides user attention
    </instruction>
    <instruction>
      Tie motion timing to scroll position instead of time-based loops.
    </instruction>
  </motion_cleanup>

  <visual_simplification>
    <instruction>
      Remove floating dots, abstract orbits, and background blobs unless they directly
      reinforce sports motion or directional flow.
    </instruction>
    <instruction>
      Reduce background decoration density by at least 60%.
    </instruction>
    <instruction>
      Let photography and typography carry the visual weight.
    </instruction>
  </visual_simplification>

  <typography_system>
    <instruction>
      Establish a strict hierarchy:
      - H1: HANUMANT 2026
      - H2: Rishihood University Sports Fest
      - Body: Maximum 2 concise lines
    </instruction>
    <instruction>
      Increase contrast between headings and body text.
    </instruction>
    <instruction>
      Avoid long paragraphs. Prioritize punchy, authoritative statements.
    </instruction>
  </typography_system>

  <cta_optimization>
    <instruction>
      Make "Register Now" the single dominant CTA.
    </instruction>
    <instruction>
      Secondary actions must be visually subordinate (outline or muted).
    </instruction>
    <instruction>
      CTAs should remain visible and legible against all backgrounds.
    </instruction>
  </cta_optimization>

  <copy_refinement>
    <instruction>
      Replace all generic motivational copy.
    </instruction>
    <instruction>
      New copy must explicitly reference:
      - Competitive sports culture
      - Rishihood University identity
      - Inter-university participation
    </instruction>
    <instruction>
      Tone: confident, athletic, grounded, not poetic or vague.
    </instruction>
  </copy_refinement>

  <information_architecture>
    <instruction>
      Introduce a compact facts strip early in the scroll:
      - Dates
      - Location
      - Number of sports
      - Prize pool
    </instruction>
    <instruction>
      Information must be scannable within 3 seconds.
    </instruction>
  </information_architecture>

  <navbar_behavior>
    <instruction>
      Navbar must be fixed at all times.
    </instruction>
    <instruction>
      Transparent on hero.
      Solid or blurred background after scrolling begins.
    </instruction>
    <instruction>
      Ensure constant contrast and legibility.
    </instruction>
  </navbar_behavior>

  <performance_constraints>
    <instruction>
      Optimize for smooth 60fps scrolling.
    </instruction>
    <instruction>
      Disable heavy parallax effects on low-end or mobile devices.
    </instruction>
    <instruction>
      Lazy-load non-critical assets.
    </instruction>
  </performance_constraints>

  <technical_preferences>
    <preference>Use GSAP or Framer Motion for scroll-linked animations.</preference>
    <preference>Use requestAnimationFrame where custom logic is needed.</preference>
    <preference>Use semantic HTML and accessible contrast ratios.</preference>
  </technical_preferences>

  <success_metrics>
    <metric>Zero visual glitches during scroll.</metric>
    <metric>Immediate clarity within first 3 seconds.</metric>
    <metric>Scroll feels cinematic and intentional.</metric>
    <metric>Site feels premium and event-worthy.</metric>
  </success_metrics>
</prompt>